SO trading could be extremely difficult
almost impossible to a lot of people and
trading and traveling is unheard of
except for me I kind of just made like
50 000 likes free just chilling on the
beach so I'm going to be telling you
guys how to trade and travel and what
are the pros and cons about it let's be
honest the whole entire point and the
goal of trading is for freedom to be
financially free do whatever you want so
you got to understand there's pros to it
but there's also cons and you got to
learn how to manage it first point is
that the huge Pro about trading is
networking so look check this clip out
from the meet and greet we just did in
Puerto Rico
all right so right now we're on our way
to do a meet and greet not how we
usually do it we usually do it at a park
uh just out in the wild but I realize
that every single time we do that
thousand thousand 500 people put up and
it's too disorganized we don't really
get to like get that one-on-one fear of
people so we reserved the whole entire
Club big shout out to Jose gallinda you
gotta sit down spot one of the best
clubs here in Puerto Rico so we're on
our way now there we just saw some
stories where we there's like a thousand
people already waiting outside I know
cop bro
all right so we're pulling on now to the
spot let's get it I want to give a big
shout out to the Aladdin Community for
over these people waited outside for
nearly two hours just to come inside big
shout out to Rocket for helping us
sponsor the event we literally bought
out the whole entire Club open bar so
that people can enjoy the time with them
and it's just crazy that all of these
people came here not only to meet us but
to be around like-minded people that
have the same drive and same ambition
and that is exactly what we strive for
and we have something bigger than this
coming in Miami very very very soon so
stay tuned and make sure to put it on
your calendars when I announce it so the
whole entire point of entrepreneurs
Traders it's you want to get to be in
the same place as like-minded people
people drove from across the island just
to come and shake their hands so I like
doing these type of events and I don't
gain anything other from it than just
shaking somebody's hand I don't we fully
buy out the club we open up the bar we
give away uh rocket accounts we
literally do this just to motivate
people and so Traders can Network
between themselves Traders I remember
when I was by myself in my parents
little closet trading and just not
having able to talk to anybody nobody
was doing in these type of events so the
fact that I'm able to do it shake these
people hand and be like bro you're on
the right track just keep going it's
what motivates me and then should
motivate you guys to like the whole
entire point of this is to network meet
other people so you get to be in these
well-known spots so you can grow your
net worth outside of trading because
trading should just be your one source
of income you get the money then you
diversify it into other assets this
leads me to my second point and another
huge Pro is you can literally make money
from anywhere I was in the beach in
Puerto Rico I clicked the cover buttons
I set and forget and I made 50 I think
it was like like 47k I mean 25 in the
two weeks that I was out of my house so
if that doesn't motivate you guys or
tell you that this is what you got to do
then I don't I don't even know what it
is because a lot of people when they
work remotely they have to be on Zoom
they have to be on a certain location
because they have to be talking to
people I don't want to talk to anybody I
just hop on my mt4 click a button set up
forget another huge Pro is since you're
on vacation you're not like stuck in
front of the computer because the whole
point of your invocation is to go out
either go to the beach if you're in
obviously in a beach if you're a skiing
you're going to go out to ski so when
you're whenever you take your trade it
forces you to get out from the computer
gets you out from just being stuck
looking at the market so whether you're
looking to enter a setup you just wait
more time for it to be ready or if
you're already in a setup you're not
watching it following it all the time I
literally took that trade that I'm
popping up right here and I completely
forgot about it the only reason why I
noticed I was in the profit is because
the Discord with the students were like
yo take profit for it I'm like yo what's
going on because you're just completely
tuned out so these are huge Pros when it
comes to trading and traveling so to
every upside there's a downside so the
same way how you can be obviously set
and forgetting while you're in profit
you can probably set and forget too much
so another con is since you're on
vacation you can probably forget about
the markets you can get a little bit Out
Of Tune since you're on vacation you
want to enjoy your time and that's fine
that's cool that's the whole entire
point of this but you gotta understand
the Market's not going to go anywhere
the probability and the opportunities to
be making money are always going to be
there in the market so a con can be a
since you're so carried away of being on
vacation maybe you can get a little bit
Out Of Tune simply because you're not
watching the markets as you should be
right so I personally myself since I
started trading five years ago there
hasn't been one single day not one
single day on the calendar obviously
other than the weekends that I haven't
looked at the markets even if it's just
a quick glance through my phone I just
simply don't feel good if I'm not
watching the markets just simply in tune
with it it's almost like my daily
routine it's like I'm one with the
market I feel like it's my friend like
I've seen it been through it I've gone
through a lot of emotional experiences
with it so I have this almost like I
don't say like spiritual attachment or
anything but I'm connected to the
markets in a way where I can't set and
forget of not watching it my next point
is time zone so after Puerto Rico I take
a one-way flight to Colombia Colombia
was lit my boys let me tell you you
gotta check it right so Colombia was
probably I think one hour uh it was
actually the same time as Miami but
since I was in Puerto Rico Puerto Rico's
one hour head of Miami so that
completely tripped me out I had no idea
what was going on I didn't even know
that was a thing I would tell the
students oh let's hop on a zoom it was
seven o'clock and they're like yo where
you at and now you know the time zone
could be effective so it depends where
you go you got to make sure you're on
top of that because if you trade New
York you can completely miss the session
or if you trade London you can pull up
too late or too early so that's
something to keep into consideration and
then the most interesting and the most
I'd say difficult of like roller coaster
when it comes to the cons is the
emotions while you're on vacation making
money so I guess I got a little bit
emotional after I made the 50k in Puerto
Rico because I'm like yo one-way flight
to Colombia I don't give a right
let's go see what's up with these
Colombian girls over there so the bad
thing is that let's say now I go to
Colombia and now I lose money my
emotions all over the place because I
just did a emotional one-way trip so you
got to understand you got to keep your
emotional state 100 so if you're making
money while you're on vacation cool
that's why you did it keep going
according to your plan but if you lose
money while you're on vacation don't out
completely throw it out the window and
now you're just you're not enjoying your
stay there anymore just keep treating it
like a business it has highs and it has
lows so if you made a lot of money on
vacation don't now go ball out go to
another spot because obviously those
profits could go up and down and if you
lose money on vacation don't let that
completely get to your mind so I hope
you guys really enjoyed this video if
you guys can tell we already hit 75k
subscribers so I appreciate every single
one of you guys and then for the next
video I'm going to be showing you guys
how I select a random subscriber and I
have something that I'm going to be
giving away for them and I have another
giveaway coming at 100K subscribers so
make sure you guys subscribe stay tuned
for the next video and I'll see you guys
let's get it